<resources>
    <string name="app_name">A Third Jetpack Compose Story</string>

    <string name="intro">

    </string>

    <string name="intro_cards">
        A mottle of defiance springs from some long-forgotten well.
    </string>

    <string name="player_movement">Walk</string>

    <string name="walking_without_enemy">You are just walking along.</string>
    <string name="encounter_enemy">You encounter %1$s.</string>

    <string name="successful_attack">You successfully attack %1$s!</string>
    <string name="failed_attack">%1$s avoids your attack, and bonks you on the head!</string>
    <string name="fight_enemy_win">You defeat %1$s!</string>
    <string name="fight_enemy_lose">You succumb to injuries from %1$s! Game over! </string>

    <!--Strength--> <string name="attack">Attack</string>
    <!--Intellect--> <string name="gaslight">Gaslight</string>
    <!--Dexterity--> <string name="run_away">Run away</string>
    <!--Willpower--> <string name="sensual">Dance\nsensually</string>

    <string-array name="enemies_easy">
        <item>a small child of indeterminate sex</item>
        <item>a teacup Chihuahua</item>
        <item>a rolling bike wheel</item>
        <item>an elderly woman using a walker</item>
        <item>a baby with a full diaper</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="enemies_easy_description">
        <item>It looks harmless. It probably is harmless. There is something wrong with one of its eyes, but you cannot discern what. It is advancing.</item>
        <item>Its slightly aft grin is K-9 reminiscent, except for a small pulsation on its neck that is too regular to be a twitch. It is trotting determinedly toward you.</item>
        <item>Physics should not account for the methodical beeline the wheel is making for you.</item>
        <item>Grandma Pie Baker this is not. She\'s slow, she\'s frail, and she\'s not getting out of your way.</item>
        <item>It\'s just sitting in front of you. A stinking, whining, inconsolable mess.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="job_events_bad">
        <item>Your boss hates you and lets you know it. Loudly.</item>
        <item>Todd from Accounting pees in your coffee again.</item>
        <item>The office receptionist forgets your name. You\'ve both worked there for 32 years.</item>
        <item>One of your clients is unhappy. He\'s a wolf, and you\'re the fattest one there.</item>
        <item>Your paycheck is missing a few zeros, and it only had a few to begin with.</item>
        <item>Your work socks have dissolved.</item>
        <item>Today\'s lunch break has been replaced with nothing.</item>
        <item>Your last cigarette tasted like a camel. The animal, not the brand.</item>
        <item>The cute one in Accounts Billable wrote you another letter proclaiming their disdain.</item>
        <item>You slip on the floor and take a bite of the floor.</item>
        <item>One of your shoes leaves the office.</item>
        <item>The ducks in your office building\'s courtyard reject your bread.</item>
        <item>Your favorite song is on the radio and you don\'t have a radio.</item>
        <item>Your laptop is on fire.</item>
        <item>Your desk is on fire.</item>
        <item>Your hair is on fire.</item>
        <item>You\'ve been demoted. You find out from a Snapple bottle cap.</item>
        <item>The whole office got together and built a life-sized effigy of you to throw things at.</item>
        <item>Your salary has been inversely tied to inflation.</item>
        <item>You are assigned the role of foot stool at the next office party.</item>
        <item>Your last zoom meeting ended in vomiting.</item>
        <item>Your latest client has decided that they are not your client.</item>
        <item>The water cooler refuses to dispense to you.</item>
        <item>Lunch consisted of sadness with a side of nothing.</item>
        <item>Your boss needs to you stay after the office closes and catch ghouls.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="job_events_good">
        <item>You\'ve been promoted! One step forward, five steps back, as they say.</item>
        <item>Your boss didn\'t spit in your face this morning.</item>
        <item>No one at the office has asked you to be their slap toy today.</item>
        <item>You find two pennies in the office courtyard fountain.</item>
        <item>You find an old shoe in the office bathroom. It kind of fits.</item>
        <item>Your office laptop has taken a break from flashing you with strobe lights.</item>
        <item>Friday\'s death match against Sven the Destroyer from IT has been cancelled.</item>
        <item>This week\'s Casual Friday will not begin with a dressing down of you.</item>
        <item>Janice from Public Relations is out of town and will not be hunting you for sport this week.</item>
        <item>You caught two ghouls last night and your boss has rewarded you with a lettuce bounty.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="finance_events_bad">
        <item>You\'ve fallen for another deposed prince scam.</item>
        <item>The IRS has attached a funnel to your money bag.</item>
        <item>Tuition for your kids has increased because the school hates you. Not your kids, but you.</item>
        <item>Your significant other\'s dollar snacking habit has accelerated</item>
        <item>Money grows on trees and you\'re in Qatar (they have no trees).</item>
        <item>Your dog needs a new head.</item>
        <item>Your dog needs a new butt.</item>
        <item>Your dog needs a new tail.</item>
        <item>Your eldest child has accelerated his training for Nathan\'s Hot Dog Eating Contest, and insists you buy only the choicest cuts of beef</item>
        <item>Your health insurer has added an ugly duckling surcharge on a sliding scale and you have broken the scale</item>
        <item>You win a sunken boat on The Price is Right and have to pay taxes on it.</item>
        <item>You win the California State Reverse Lottery and owe the jackpot.</item>
        <item>Your dog has given birth to duodecaplets and they all have expensive diseases.</item>
        <item>The neighborhood cat is blackmailing you.</item>
        <item>You catch your neighbor cheating on his wife and he\'s somehow blackmailing you.</item>
        <item>The Hamburglar is upset at your lack of hams, and takes money instead.</item>
        <item>Subway is no longer honoring your free sandwich cards. Just yours.</item>
        <item>The local recycling center now requires items to be doofus-free.</item>
        <item>Your dollar-bill phobia is starting to catch up to you.</item>
        <item>Your custom medical-grade deodorant has doubled in price.</item>
        <item>You get a speeding ticket while sitting on your porch.</item>
        <item>Walmart decides to sue you again.</item>
        <item>The police are demanding more bribes to protect you from yourself.</item>
        <item>Your collection of newspaper hats has declined in value.</item>
        <item>China has decided it will no longer prop you up economically.</item>
        <item>You are required by a court to pay alimony. You are still married.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="finance_events_good">
        <item>You bet against yourself in a beauty contest and win.</item>
        <item>One of your deposed prince scammers feels guilty and return a bit of the money.</item>
        <item>You are mistaken by aid workers for a charity case.</item>
        <item>You find a quarter in your youngest child\'s ear. Are there more?</item>
        <item>Your Roth IRA has synergized the actuated backward overflow of depreciated commercial assets.</item>
        <item>The bank teller is about to quit and commit seppuku, and decides to give you extra money.</item>
        <item>Your significant other decides to put the whole family on an oxygen-only cleanse, which is pretty cheap.</item>
        <item>The ringing in your ears turns out to be just a bunch of silver dollars.</item>
        <item>Someone lands on Boardwalk and you don\'t have it mortgaged.</item>
        <item>Your car returns home and forgives you.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="family_events_bad">
        <item>Your significant other hates you. That\'s it. That\'s the whole thing.</item>
        <item>Your significant other reminds you that this is a green card arrangement.</item>
        <item>Your significant other leaves you poisoned hot dogs for dinner.</item>
        <item>Your youngest child deflates your car tires in front of you. You are helpless to stop it.</item>
        <item>Your eldest child introduces you to their date as \"that creepy old neighbor\".</item>
        <item>Your children declare they are on strike until you are less ugly.</item>
        <item>The mail now includes love letters that are not for you.</item>
        <item>Your new couples therapist has declared you an albatross.</item>
        <item>The family dog has declared for your significant other.</item>
        <item>The neighborhood cat has declared for your significant other.</item>
        <item>The neighborhood shrew has declared for your significant other.</item>
        <item>Your significant other has ordered \"The Marriage Defuser\" from QVC.</item>
        <item>A baby has arrived at your doorstep. It declares you a bad parent and leaves.</item>
        <item>Your mother-in-law has declared you an enemy of the state.</item>
        <item>Your father-in-law has declared you an enemy of the state.</item>
        <item>Your brother-in-law has declared you an enemy of the state.</item>
        <item>Everyone was invited to the family reunion except you. Literally everyone. In the world.</item>
        <item>Your fifth cousin is no longer the kissing cousin.</item>
        <item>Your parents tell you that adoption records are a cruel joke.</item>
        <item>Your parents replace you in their family photos with Macaulay Culkin</item>
        <item>You receive a Google alert about another life insurance policy opened in your name.</item>
        <item>Your significant other has decided to get your name tattooed on the leg she uses for life mistakes.</item>
        <item>You arrive home to discover the same state of dismal, quiet desperation as when you left.</item>
        <item>Your middle child takes a picture of Ted Lasso to \"Take Your Father to Work Day\"</item>
        <item>Your family has decided there is no room in the house for you tonight.</item>
        <item>Your birth parents have decided to let you visit home, provided you wear a mask.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="family_events_good">
        <item>You find the birthday card you bought for yourself when your family forgot. It still smells like whiskey.</item>
        <item>Your family has decided to suspend the daily \"Two Minutes of Hate\" directed at you.</item>
        <item>Your youngest child had stopped asking you to hide in the closet when her friends come over.</item>
        <item>Your couples therapist no longer feels you\'re 105 percent to blame.</item>
        <item>The family dog has decided to let you make eye contact again.</item>
        <item>The neighborhood cat has stopped using you as a scratching post. For now.</item>
        <item>Your significant other has stopped comparing you unfavorably to their side bae.</item>
        <item>Another state has deemed you human and now recognizes your marriage.</item>
        <item>Your mother-in-law has stopped sending you hourly hate mail. For now.</item>
        <item>Your father-in-law has stopped burning effigies of you on Facebook Live. For now.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="social_life_bad">
        <item>Still no friend requests on Facebook. Do people still use Facebook?</item>
        <item>One of your last twitter followers has unfollowed, citing irreconcilable differences.</item>
        <item>Your old MySpace page has been sold to a Russian circus.</item>
        <item>Instagram no longer allows you to post selfies, citing public health concerns.</item>
        <item>TikTok has reduced the length of your videos to 0 seconds.</item>
        <item>Your high school reunion has sent you a "Not Invited" invitation.</item>
        <item>Your grade school crush still hates you. Still.</item>
        <item>Your old college bae has been arrested for being a goat.</item>
        <item>Your best invisible friend has decided that things are not working out.</item>
        <item>The stranger whom you donated a kidney to is trying to give it back.</item>
        <item>The love letter you sent into space has been returned. On fire.</item>
        <item>Your best non-invisible friend turns out to be invisible.</item>
        <item>The city has decided you need to be quarantined for a month. Just because.</item>
        <item>The local pet shelter is trying to hire you to show the animals that \'things could be worse\."</item>
        <item>You are known as \"Moses\" at the local watering hole because people just part for you.</item>
        <item>Your local Wednesday night Bingo club informs you that your personality needs an overhaul.</item>
        <item>Strippers have begun throwing dollars at you. Silver dollars. At your head.</item>
        <item>Your significant other\'s side bae no longer wants to be friends.</item>
        <item>Your local church has started replacing \"Hell\" with \"Locked in a room with you\."</item>
        <item>The talent at a weekly comedy show decides to abandon their sets and just heckle you for 2 hours.</item>
        <item>Goodwill rejects your clothes, citing crimes against humanity.</item>
        <item>The \"Big Sibling\" program has decided to close down and euthanize its clients after meeting you.</item>
        <item>The Starbucks barista writes \"God Has Forsaken Me\" on your drink.</item>
        <item>You have no friends. That\'s it.</item>
        <item>Parking Enforcement has ticketed your car as being \"abandoned\" with you in it.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="social_life_good">
        <item>Your grade school dog has come back to life, "\Pet Semetary\" style, and you have a pleasant evening cannibalising with them. </item>
        <item>The Starbucks barista allows you to make eye contact.</item>
        <item>You are accepted by a cult of cult addicts, and it\'s not terrible.</item>
        <item>Your eldest child\'s friends decide to stop bullying you for a day, and let you sniff glue with them.</item>
        <item>You go fishing with colleagues and they do not force you to be the bait.</item>
        <item>You have been unbanned from social media outlets, citing the new federal policy against animal cruelty</item>
        <item>You rack up a high score on Skee-Ball at the local bar and for a moment, everyone doesn\'t hate you.</item>
        <item>Your knee-jerk plan at faking a deadly illness for sympathy works.</item>
        <item>You get mail addressed to \"Local Resident,"\, and you know you are loved.</item>
        <item>The local church allows you to attend services again, if only to make up for latest molestation scandal.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>